Get your motor runnin'
Head out on the highway
Lookin' for adventure
And whatever comes our way
Yeah Darlin' go make it happen
Take the world in a love embrace
Fire all of your guns at once &
Explode into space
I like smoke and lightning
Heavy metal thunder
Racin' with the wind
And the feelin' that I'm under
Yeah Darlin' go make it happen
Take the world in a love embrace
Fire all of your guns at once &
Explode into space
And like a true nature's child
We were born, born to be wild
We can climb so high
I never wanna die
Born to be wild
Get your motor runnin'
Head out on the highway
Lookin' for adventure
And whatever comes our way
Yeah Darlin' go make it happen
Take the world in a love embrace
Fire all of your guns at once &
Explode into space
And like a true nature's child
We were born, born to be wild
We can climb so high
I never wanna die
Born to wild
Born to be wild